Why is this black people's business?
We've got to be here for them.
These are brothers.
These are our sisters.
Because if we're not all free, then who frees?
We've got to help people.
They'll be impressed everywhere.
The taxes that they're using over there, they already did it here.
And when MOVE, when they bombed MOVE in Philadelphia,
when they bombed Tulsa, Oklahoma, when they committed all those race riots.
It's happening not only in Palestine.
It's happening in the Caribbean.
It's happening in Latin America.
It's happening all over the world.
The U.S. war machine needs to be stopped.
We must come together on a united front to defeat white supremacy.
Because Israel is a white supremacist state.
We were marching down in Ferguson.
They were the main ones showing us how to, like, blockade the cops off.
And they were getting the same tear gas as us.
The fact that black people are policed in such violent, militarized ways
is the same exact reason why Palestinians are being policed in such violent and militarized way.
We're not free until they're free.
They're not free until we're free.
We have to fight together.